A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42414)., Extent: 47.95 cubic feet (137 boxes). (Box 38-174)
  - 2003 Session
    - Senate
      - SB 977 (03) Commonwealth Transportation Board (CTB), etc. (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 978 (03) Insurance; Claims Experience Data (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 979 (03) Identity Theft (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 980 (03) Powers of Fiduciaries in Will or Trust; Extending Scope (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 981 (03) Public Finance Act; Appeals from Bond Validation Proceedings (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 982 (03) Public Finance Act; Applicability (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - SB 984 (03) Lawyers Helping Lawyers; Civil Immunity (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 985 (03) Anonymous Plaintiff (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 987 (03) School Buses; Display of American Flag Decals (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 988 (03) Prepayable Fines for Traffic Infractions (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 989 (03) Child Labor; Exemptions (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 990 (03) Condemnation; Reimbursement of Property Taxes (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 991 (03) Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court Expanded Jurisdiction (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 992 (03) Subpoena Duces Tecum; Financial Institutions; Credit Card Companies (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 993 (03) Motor Vehicle Insurance; Uninsured Motorist Coverage (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB 995 (03) Eminent Domain; Copy of Title Report (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 997 (03) Mortgages; Priority (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 998 (03) Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 999 (03) Negotiable Instruments; Return of Paid Instruments (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 1001 (03) Administrative Process Act; Fast-Track Rulemaking Process (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 1002 (03) Reports/Records by Chief Medical Examiner Admissible; Civil/Criminal (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 1003 (03) Victims' Rights (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 1004 (03) Darrell Green Boulevard (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - SB 1007 (03) Recodification of Title 25; Eminent Domain; Condemnation (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - SB 1008 (03) Medical Assistance Services; Consumer-Directed Care (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1010 (03) Notification; Cancer Patients; Reports; Statewide Cancer Registry (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1012 (03) Dept. of Human Resource Management; Criminal Background Checks (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1013 (03) Conservation of Trees During Localities' Development (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1014 (03) Unemployment Compensation; Social Security Benefit (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1018 (03) Economic Development Authorities (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1019 (03) Driving While Intoxicated; Penalty (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1025 (03) Higher Education; Approval of Certain Terms (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - SB 1026 (03) Income Tax; Subtraction; Payments Received by Contract Poultry Growers (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1027 (03) Division of Risk Management (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1030 (03) Virginia Tax Amnesty Program (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1032 (03) Local "Crime Stoppers" (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1033 (03) Real Estate Tax; Situs for Assessment of Motor Vehicles (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1034 (03) Virginia Health Spa Act (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1036 (03) General Assembly; Submission of Reports and Executive Summaries (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - SB 1038 (03) Virginia Retirement System; Creditable Compensation (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1039 (03) Notice of Unemployment Benefit Charges and Taxes (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1040 (03) Unemployment Compensation; Base Period (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1043 (03) Child Protective Services; Investigation Procedures (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1044 (03) Dept. of General Services; Division of Purchases and Supply; Purchases (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1045 (03) Pounds and Animal Shelters; Penalties (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1047 (03) Economic Development Authorities (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1048 (03) Equine Liability (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - SB 1049 (03) Income Tax; Conformity of Terms to the Internal Revenue Code (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - SB 1051 (03) Virginia Water Facilities Revolving Fund (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - SB 1052 (03) Preservation of Important Farmlands (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - SB 1053 (03) Conservation Easements; Requirements to be a Holder (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - SB 1055 (03) Charter; City of Lexington (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - SB 1058 (03) Licenses; Identification Cards; Fraudulent Representation; Penalty (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - SB 1060 (03) Child Protection Act; Mandatory Counseling; Detention (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1064 (03) Dept. of General Services; Public Procurement Act; Hiring Ex-Felons (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1066 (03) Disposal of Trash or Cutting of Weeds (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1068 (03) Health; Local Health Partnership Authorities (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1069 (03) Sheriffs; Courthouse Security (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1071 (03) Sale of Drugs On or Near Certain Properties; Penalty (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1074 (03) Golf Carts (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1075 (03) Fees for Solid Waste Disposal (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1076 (03) Purchase of Service Handgun (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - SB 1077 (03) Juvenile Criminal Records (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1078 (03) Confidentiality of Department of Juvenile Justice Records (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1081 (03) Health Insurance; Mandated Coverage for Morbid Obesity Treatment (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1082 (03) Protocol for Testing Children for Elevated Blood-Lead Levels (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1083 (03) Sharing Protected Health Information Between State Agencies (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1088 (03) Land Application of Sewage Sludge; Requirements and Regulations (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1090 (03) Dental Hygienists' Possession and Administration of Certain Drugs (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1091 (03) Health Care Data Reporting (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - SB 1092 (03) Department of Veterans Services (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1093 (03) Highway Safety Corridors (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1094 (03) Small Water or Sewer Public Utility Act Rate Increases (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1095 (03) City of Roanoke Real Estate Tax Rates (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1096 (03) Income Tax Refund; Contribution to the Art Museum of Western Virginia (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1097 (03) Parent Education; Custody, Visitation, and Support Cases (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1099 (03) Joint Schools (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - SB 1101 (03) Recodification of Title 63.2; Corrections Bill (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - SB 1102 (03) Creation of Fair Housing Board at the Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - SB 1103 (03) Mortgage Lender and Broker Act; Predatory Practices (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - SB 1107 (03) Administration of Elections and Election Procedures; Penalties (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - SB 1112 (03) Bicycles (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - SB 1117 (03) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Wine Shippers' Licenses (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - SB 1121 (03) Criminal Background Checks; Victims of Domestic Violence (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - SB 1122 (03) Virginia Property Owners' Association Act; Amendment to Declaration (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - SB 1123 (03) Estate Tax (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - SB 1124 (03) Parental Consent for Abortion; Penalty (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - SB 1125 (03) Income Tax Returns of Affiliated Corporations (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - SB 1128 (03) Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - SB 1129 (03) Court Fees and Costs (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - SB 1131 (03) Insurance Notices (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - SB 1132 (03) Workers' Compensation; Notice Procedures (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - SB 1133 (03) Unclaimed Property; Demutualization Proceeds (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1134 (03) Commonwealth's Right to Appeal (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1135 (03) Crimes; Money Laundering (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1137 (03) Transporting Wastes on State Waters (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1138 (03) Larceny; Penalties (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1139 (03) Computer Crimes; Enhanced Penalties; Forfeiture (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - SB 1140 (03) Stun Weapons or Tasers (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1143 (03) Final Judgments in Circuit Court; When Modifiable and Appealable (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1145 (03) Virginia State Crime Commission (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1146 (03) Jail Policies (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1149 (03) Sexually Violent Predators (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1151 (03) Protection of Infants (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - SB 1152 (03) Virginia Racing Commission; Powers, Local Referenda; Prohibitions; Penalties (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1153 (03) Child Pornography Images Registry (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1154 (03) Motor Vehicle Insurance; Exclusion of Named Persons (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1156 (03) Solicitation of Contributions; Commercial Co-Venturers (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1157 (03) Child Support Income Withholding; Service of Process (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1160 (03) Disposition of the Unrestorably Incompetent Defendant (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1161 (03) Parking; Arlington County (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - SB 1162 (03) Crime Victim Rights (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1164 (03) Sex Offender and Crimes Against Minors Registry (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1168 (03) Mandatory Connection to Water and Sewage Systems in Certain Counties (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1169 (03) Medical Treatment of Inmates; Financial Responsibility (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1172 (03) Charter; Town of Bluefield (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1173 (03) Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy Permit Fees (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1174 (03) Buchanan County Tourist Train Development Authority (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - SB 1177 (03) D. Woodrow Bird Memorial Highway (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1180 (03) Property Conveyance; National Guard Armory (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1181 (03) Excursion Trains (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1182 (03) Housing; Appointment of Commissioners of Regional Housing Authorities (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1183 (03) Real Property Tax; Installment Agreements to Pay Delinquent Taxes (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1186 (03) State Water Safety Zones and Restricted Areas; Penalty (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1187 (03) Fees of Public Notaries (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1188 (03) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Access to Cable TV (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - SB 1189 (03) Economic Development Authorities (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1190 (03) Youthful Drivers (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1193 (03) Regulation of Stormwater (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1194 (03) Real Estate Brokerage Subsidiaries of Banks (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1195 (03) Health Maintenance Organizations; Powers (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1199 (03) Locomotives (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1200 (03) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Farm Winery Licenses (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1201 (03) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Farm Wineries; Shipments (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - SB 1202 (03) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Class A Farm Wineries (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1203 (03) Virginia FOIA; Electronic Communication Meetings (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1204 (03) Code Adam Alerts; Virginia Amber Alert Program (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1205 (03) Partial Birth Infanticide (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1206 (03) Child Support; Liens; Publication of Delinquent Parent List (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1209 (03) Medical Fees in Certain Criminal Cases to be Taxed as Costs (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1210 (03) Crimes; Peeping (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - SB 1212 (03) State Mandates on Local Governments (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1218 (03) Children's Health Insurance (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1220 (03) Parking; Localities (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1221 (03) Water Supply Planning (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1222 (03) Urban Highway System Construction Funds (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1224 (03) EMT's Authorization to Possess and Administer Epinephrine (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1225 (03) Commercial Driver's Licenses; Hazardous Materials Endorsement (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - SB 1226 (03) Certificate of Public Need; Regulations Cancer Care Center Services (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1227 (03) Local Taxes; Administrative Fees to Collect Delinquent Taxes/Charges (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1229 (03) Public-Private Transportation Act of 1995 (PPTA) (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1230 (03) License Plates; Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1231 (03) Peninsula Airport Commission (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1233 (03) Crimes; Damage to Business Reputation, Etc. (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1234 (03) False Reports to Law-Enforcement Officials (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1235 (03) Charter; Town of Gretna (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1236 (03) Charter; Town of Chatham (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - SB 1239 (03) Death Penalty; Mental Retardation (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - SB 1240 (03) Special Conservators of the Peace (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - SB 1243 (03) Class and Beneficiaries; When Determined (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - SB 1244 (03) Industrial Development Authorities; Russell County (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - SB 1246 (03) Support Payments to Department of Juvenile Justice (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - SB 1247 (03) Information Technology Investment Board; Chief Information Officer (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - SB 1249 (03) Avian Influenza (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1250 (03) Prehospital Patient Care Reports; Disclosure (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1251 (03) Fee for Failure to Appear (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1253 (03) Joint Commission on Health Care (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1255 (03) State Council of Higher Education; Appointment of Members (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1256 (03) Charter; City of Poquoson (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - SB 1258 (03) Fees for Driving Under the Influence Conviction (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - SB 1261 (03) Preneed Funeral Contracts Through Irrevocable Trusts (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - SB 1263 (03) Courier Vehicles (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - SB 1264 (03) Health Care Data Reporting (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1267 (03) Health; Certificate of Birth Resulting in Stillbirth (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1274 (03) Easements; Definition of Enjoyment (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1275 (03) Division of Consolidated Laboratory Services; Environmental Lab Certification (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1276 (03) Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), Customer Service Pilot Project (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1278 (03) Charitable Gaming; Creation of the Dept. of Charitable Gaming (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - SB 1279 (03) Rail Transportation Development Authority (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1280 (03) Persons Who May Perform Marriage Rites (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1284 (03) Use of Credit Information in Insurance Transactions (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1285 (03) Local Real Estate Assessments; Buildings; Completed or Fit for Use (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1288 (03) In Camera Interviews in Child Custody or Visitation Hearings (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1290 (03) Occupancy Permits (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - SB 1291 (03) Industrial Development Authorities; Bonds (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1293 (03) Professions and Occupations; Prior Criminal History (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1295 (03) Voluntary Settlements Among Local Governments; Acceptance of Proffers (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1296 (03) Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation (DPOR); Polygraph Examiners (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1298 (03) Parental Rights (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1302 (03) DUI; Restricted License (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1305 (03) Conveyance of Easement (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1306 (03) Child Protective Services; Retention of Records (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - SB 1307 (03) State Corporation Commission (SCC) Regulation of Sewer Utilities (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1308 (03) Establishing Trust for Coal Interests (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1315 (03) Clarifications for Certain Collegial Bodies (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1316 (03) Medical Malpractice Joint Underwriting Association; Activation (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1318 (03) Regional Housing Authorities; Appointment of Commissioners (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1324 (03) Real Estate Board; Continuing Education for Licensees (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - SB 1327 (03) Limited Licenses to Certain Graduates of Foreign Medical Schools (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1329 (03) Board of Accountancy; Powers; Penalty (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1330 (03) Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Acts of 2002 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1332 (03) Sex Offender and Crimes Against Minors Registry (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1333 (03) Departments of Real Estate; Goochland County (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1334 (03) Health Regulatory Boards; Disciplinary Procedure Report Requirements (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1336 (03) Resisting Arrest (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - SB 1337 (03) Collection of Local License Fees by Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1338 (03) Mental Examination Report (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1340 (03) Solicitation of Contributions; Federated Fund-Raising Organizations (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1341 (03) Prescription Assistance Mechanisms (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1343 (03) Attendance of Witnesses; Production of Evidence to Legislative Bodies (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1344 (03) Electronic Meetings; UVA Board of Visitors; Video Broadcasting Meetings (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1345 (03) Criminal Justice Training Academies; Fees (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1351 (03) Procurement by the Department of Transportation; Lighting Systems (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - SB 1354 (03) Date and Time Stamp Required to be Affixed to Recorded Documents (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part one) (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part two) (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part three) (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part four) (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part five) (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part six) (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part seven) (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part eight) (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part nine) (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part ten) (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Acts of Assembly 2003 Session (part eleven) (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Action Summaries
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 1375-HB 1597 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 1608-HB 1836 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 1847-HB 2065 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 2068-HB 2214 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 2228-HB 2625 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Administration, House of Delegates, HB 2626-HJ 646 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Secretary of Administration, Senate, SB 702-SB 793 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Administration, Senate, SB 812-SB 1012 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Administration, Senate, SB 1036-SB 1235 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Administration, Senate, SB 1236-SJ 359 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, House of Delegates, HB 1431-HB 1953 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, House of Delegates, HB 1989-HJR 588 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Senate, SB 761-SB 1318 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Education, House of Delegates, HB 1376-HB 1638 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Education, House of Delegates, HB 1639-HB 2348 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Education, House of Delegates, HB 2349-HJR 592 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Education, Senate, SB 659-SB 864 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Secretary of Education, Senate, SB 938-SB 1213 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 1387-HB 1602 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 1603-HB 1755 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 1776-HB 2045 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 2047-HB 2277 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 2306-HB 2490 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 2503-HB 2688 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Finance, House of Delegates, HB 2693-HB 2828 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Finance, Senate, SB 704-SB 900 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Finance, Senate, SB 901-SB 1095 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Finance, Senate, SB 1096-SJ 347 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1402-HB 1524 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1535-HB 1685 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1688-HB 1740 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1741-HB 1835 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1844-HB 2006 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2007-HB 2097 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2105-HB 2221 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2225-HB 2287 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2288-HB 2332 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2346-HB 2405 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2412-HB 2494 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2513-HB 2597 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, House of Delegates, HB 2605-HB 2833 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 727-SB 839 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 841-SB 926 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 931-SB 1079 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 1081-SB 1149 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 1150-SB 1216 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 1218-SB 1288 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Senate, SB 1298-SB 1341 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Natural Resources, House of Delegates, HB 1883-HB 2632 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Secretary of Natural Resources, Senate, SB 914-SJ 381 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Public Safety, House of Delegates, HB 1432-HB 2121 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Secretary of Technology, House of Delegates and Senate (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Secretary of Transportation, House of Delegates, HB 1374-HB 1488 (Box 105, Folder 8)